William Berry

Wberry264@gmail.com (502)724-0232 /in/wberry264/ https://github.com/WilJonze

SUMMARY

Enthusiastic Web Development student at Code Louisville with 6+ years of experience in the designing, building, and testing of unique electrical systems. A keen interest in the construction of creative quality applications that help meet a need for the everyday person. Motivated and quick learner looking to prove technical capabilities and understanding. Committed to becoming a Full Stack Developer by 2023.

SKILLS

- Project Management
- Command Line
- Git/Github
- HTML/CSS

WORK EXPERIENCE

Electrician

Mar 2016 - Present

IBEW 369 (various contractors)

Louisville, KY

- Installation of all aspects of an electrical systems including the installation of motors, motor controls, transformers, and electrical panels.
- As Foreman Maintained key elements of project management, OSHA compliance, construction timelines, state
 and federal code requirements, apprentice training, inventory management and purchasing.
 - Managed jobs that added to approximately \$500,000+ in volume.
 - Supervised and completed high intensity jobs within a short time frame.
- Designed and installed several Ethernet Cable and Fiber Optic systems including assessing customer needs,
 Ethernet and fiber optic termination, physical connection to server, and collaboration with IT for testing.

Cafe Manager

Jan 2014 - Mar 2016

Starbucks Coffee (Seelbach Hotel)

Louisville, KY

- Managed Day to Day operations, manpower, inventory, and customer service expectations.
- Collected, processed, and evaluated various sales data, while working with upper management to implement future goals.
- Coordinated with other department heads within the hotel to capitalize sales during key events within the city.

EDUCATION

Code Louisville 2022-Current Web Development Louisville, KY